[The Heir]
[Episode 24]
As the head of the family, I, Li Zhen,
propose
hanging his portrait in the ancestral hall
so he may receive
the Li family's offerings
alongside our ancestor, Li Tinggui.
Hang...
Hanging his portrait
in the ancestral hall?
Zhen, are you serious?
Sixth Grandfather deserves it.
Just as you said,
Sixth Grandfather risked his life
to bring back this batch of pine timber.
We can't just hand it over like this.
But if we insist
on defending the pine timber at all costs
while ignoring the Li family's crisis,
we will only further betray
his life's work.
So,
Uncle Jingdong,
we have to give them
this batch of pine timber.
However,
we can't give it for free.
Get out!
-Get out!
Get out of Li Ink Workshop!
What is this?
Don't come closer!
The 7 days are up!
Hand over the pine timber now!
I don't care about the 7 days!
If you come any closer,
I'll kill you!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Uncle Jingdong!
Calm down! Calm down!
Stop, stop!
Put down the axe first!
Yes!
Put it down!
I'll ask you one thing!
Are we keeping
the pine timber or not?
Put it down first!
Let's talk!
I'll go talk to them! Okay?
Li Jingdong,
you don't need to play tough
to threaten me.
I'm here on the order of the government.
I must get
this batch of pine timber.
Go!
Who dares!
If you come any closer!
What are you doing?
I'll kill myself!
Every single one of you
will have to pay for my life!
Even if I become a ghost,
-I won't let you go!
-Uncle Jingdong!
Stop messing around, okay?
Put down the axe first! Put it down!
Gentlemen, there's no need to fear him.
Today, Li Jingdong obstructed you
in carrying out imperial orders first.
Even if he dies,
the Tian family will take responsibility.
Go!
Don't do it!
What are you doing?
Master!
Who dares come any closer?
Don't do it!
On the pine timber,
I have sprinkled
rosin ash!
If anyone takes a step forward,
we will die together!
Are you crazy?
Uncle Jingdong,
I'm begging you.
Can you put down the tinder?
Sixth Grandfather risked his life
to get this batch of pine timber.
If you burn it all—
have you thought about Sixth Grandfather?
This pine timber—
I'd rather burn it and offer it to
my dead father than let them waste it!
Don't you dare, Li Jingdong!
Don't come over!
What are you trying to do?
Don't go over there!
Don't!
Don't you know Li Jingdong's temper?
If he really burns it,
how will you answer to the authorities?
Back off!
Everyone, back off!
Alright, alright!
Back off! Back off!
Go!
Li Zhen.
Name your condition.
As long as you can hold back
that stubborn mule Li Jingdong,
whatever compensation you want,
we can discuss.
That's easy for you to say.
With the pine wilt disease
raging outside right now,
the value of this batch of pine timber
is immeasurable to begin with.
Besides, it is
what Sixth Grandfather sacrificed
his life for.
No matter how huge the compensation,
Uncle Jingdong wouldn't agree.
Everything
has a price.
I'll pay you 3 times the market price
for the pine timber.
That comes to 300 taels.
What do you think?
Three hundred taels?
Go talk to him yourself.
Five hundred taels.
This is the absolute maximum.
Tian Benchang,
why don't you understand?
It's not about the money.
Sixth Grandfather sacrificed his life
for this batch of pine timber.
It was for the future of Li Ink.
A little petty profit
is not enough
to make Uncle Jingdong back down.
Don't you get it?
Zhen,
then tell me,
what exactly do you want?
If you can
give me ten years' right of use
of the Tian family's Linxi pine yard,
I might be able to find a way
to talk to him.
Linxi pine yard is also suffering
from pine wilt disease.
What do you want it for?
To cut down all the pines
and plant tung trees instead.
Tung tree seedlings
take only 3 years to grow and produce oil.
But the impact of the pine wilt disease
will last for several three-year cycles.
Only by replacing pine soot with oil soot
can we ensure
the long-term survival of Li Ink.
Moreover,
Linxi pine yard
is the largest pine yard in Huizhou.
Since I have decided
to change the production method of Li Ink,
I naturally need a piece of land
to plant these tung trees.
Even so,
ten years
is too long.
That is the only way
I can think of right now.
If you don't agree,
then we have nothing to talk about.
Please leave.
My father has deep feelings
for Linxi pine yard.
I cannot agree to this on my own.
I must go back and discuss it with him.
Then, Eldest Young Master Tian,
you'd better reach a decision quickly.
Even if I can afford to wait,
Uncle Jingdong may not be able to wait.
With his temper,
if he loses his mind one day
and burns all the pine timber,
I won't
be able to help.
Wait for my news.
Uncle Jingdong.
Did you get hurt?
I'm fine.
How did it go?
He left.
Is this lampblack
really made from rosin oil?
Yes.
Yesterday I went to the Li pine yard
and dug it out myself.
Everyone is cutting down pines
because of the pine wilt disease.
Few people know
about the rosin under the pines.
Zhen,
it's amazing that you thought of this.
So, Zhen, you mean
using the rosin oil from the pine trees
in the Li pine yard
to solve this material shortage crisis?
Uncle Jingdong,
what I want
is more than that.
Now the Tian family controls
the Linxi pine yard
that once belonged to the Luo family.
And this pine yard
is currently the largest
and oldest pine yard in Huizhou.
I want the right to use Linxi pine yard.
You mean
using our pine timber to trade for
the right to use the Linxi pine yard,
and then dig out
the rosin oil under the pines there
for our use?
Exactly.
If we can get this pine yard,
then for the next few years,
our Li family
will no longer lack pine lampblack,
and the quality will be top-notch.
However,
Tian Benchang
is always suspicious.
Even with the pine wilt disease,
he won't just give the pine yard to us.
So today,
I want to discuss it with you,
Grandpa, Uncle Jingdong.
Now,
I've made it known
that the Li family
will switch to planting tung trees.
I also asked Master Qi to contact
tung tree seedling vendors.
Using this as a cover,
we can secretly collect rosin oil
without attracting anyone's attention.
Also,
if the Tian family comes again,
I'll need Uncle Jingdong
to put on a show with me,
pretending to fight over the pines
and have a falling out.
I must let Tian Benchang know
that for this deal,
he can only negotiate with me
to get this batch of pine timber.
I see.
Zhen,
just tell me how to act.
Should I go all out or hold back?
Just act like Tian Jiangyue did.
The crazier, the better.
What's the situation
with Tian Benchang now?
Given his suspicious nature,
getting him to believe most of it
is already good enough.
We still need to work on the rest.
Okay.
Uncle Jingdong,
thank you for your understanding.
I know
that for you,
giving up this batch of pine timber
is not easy.
I should be thanking you.
You came up with such a good idea.
I have a bad temper.
About what happened before,
please don't take it to heart.
Speaking of bad tempers,
I'm no better than you.
We
have the same temper.
We are both from the Li family.
I thought Li Zhen
would hold out this time.
I was planning to use this
to pin a charge on her.
I didn't expect her to give in so easily.
She's smart.
Father,
what do you think about this?
Since this girl Li Zhen has given in,
she has likely offended the hardliners
in the Li family.
Li Zhen asked for the Linxi pine yard
to plant tung trees.
That's an idea.
But there are still some things
that don't make sense.
The price of tung oil is high now,
but it will definitely drop later.
If the Li family
wants to make oil soot ink,
they can just buy it
when the price is low.
It's not worth planting tung trees
on a large scale.
She didn't even consider this?
She only makes ink at home all day.
When it comes to business,
she is a bit short-sighted after all.
She's far worse than you.
Perhaps.
Anyway, I'll go check it out
these two days
and wait a bit before replying.
Aren't you going to ask me
how things are going?
I...
I was waiting for you to finish your tea.
Don't mention it.
As you requested,
I spread the fake news
about buying tung tree seedlings.
And all the seedling merchants in Huizhou
came to me.
I did sign a few orders,
but I didn't dare to waste any more money,
so I hurried back.
What about your end?
Did Tian agree to trade
the Linxi pine yard for your pine timber?
The Tian family hasn't replied yet.
If we wait any longer,
this order will be delayed.
The Tians are all scumbags.
Except for your friend.
Zhen,
how about this?
Let's first dig out the rosin oil from
the Li pine yard for the time being.
Absolutely not.
Tian Benchang is hesitating now
because he suspects this matter.
If he finds out,
our entire plan will fall through.
Master Qi, we'll have to
keep up this act—
and make it even more convincing.
Continue buying tung tree seedlings.
Ask around everywhere
and buy from everywhere.
And most importantly,
Tian Benchang
must see it with his own eyes.
The sooner the Tian family agrees,
the sooner we can begin work.
Okay, got it.
I'll try to get more done with less money.
Master, he is here.
Enjoy.
This contract for the tung tree seedlings
was handled very well.
Master Qi?
We haven't seen each other for a while.
Somehow, things already feel so different.
Young Master Tian?
Please, sit.
Sit.
Excuse me.
I almost forgot—
the Tian family is honored to supply
pine soot ink to the imperial court
because of Li Ink's help.
Yes.
I heard you now take orders
from the Li family.
Allow me to offer tea in place of wine
as thanks.
You are the lackey of a heretic.
Shameless.
What are you talking about?
Young Master Tian,
Xiao Qi is ignorant.
I'll drink this tea instead of wine.
Let's drink.
Young Master Tian,
what do you mean by that?
The Sage's reputation
must not be tarnished.
Please, Master Qi,
control your dog.
You...
Young Master Tian, I think there's
something wrong with your eyes.
I don't see any dog here.
Xiao Qi is my brother.
For what just happened,
consider it my punishment on his behalf.
Do you have any other business?
If not,
I still have duties to attend to
at the Li family.
Farewell.
Master Qi.
No need to rush.
Let me treat you to a pot of tea.
Have some tea before you go.
Please bring us your best Shengjin tea.
Okay!
Young Master Tian,
why go to such expense?
We haven't seen each other
for a long time,
and your temperament
has changed quite a bit.
It seems that
even with her own people,
Li Zhen is still hard to deal with.
She's actually managed
to turn a proper man like you
into a spineless puppet.
Interesting.
Enjoy, sir.
Keep the change.
Thank you, sir.
You are indeed generous.
True.
Now that you've lost your status,
it's only natural to be submissive.
Originally, this tea
was truly worthy of
that generous Master Qi.
What a pity.
Its aroma is too fine
for a mere ink workshop worker.
Now,
it suits you.
You dog.
You are the dog!
Just wait till you fall into my hands!
Xiao Qi.
Master, how can you still have the mood
to eat?
He just humiliated you like that.
Why are we putting up with this?
Sit down. I'll tell you the reason.
Xiao Qi.
When a villain gains power,
you have to let him flaunt it.
For now,
if we want him to say yes to Miss Li Zhen,
we need him to become arrogant—
and then overreach.
Besides, we've already endured this long.
Does it matter if we wait a little longer?
I'll settle new
and old scores with him together.
I'm so pissed!
Drink the expensive one.
Fourth Young Lady, big news.
Big news?
Good or bad?
Bad.
No, it's actually good.
For that batch of pine timber,
Li Zhen and the Sixth Branch have nearly
fallen out completely.
Li Zhen is now giving away the pine timber
and plans to switch to planting
tung tree seedlings instead.
The ink workshop is in a state of panic.
I asked Mr. Liu, who's familiar with us,
about it.
He said the ink-makers
are very dissatisfied with Li Zhen—
and some are even threatening to quit.
This is truly heaven helping us.
Take this money and give it to Mr. Liu.
Tell him to take the lead in
making trouble for Li Zhen.
As long as someone dares
to take the first step,
the others will follow suit.
Yes.
Wait.
Tell him to make
as much trouble as possible.
If he really has to leave Li Ink,
I will make up his monthly salary.
Yes.
Steward Shao, look.
On the 22nd,
we received 100 soot cakes.
What's going on here?
Steward Shao, I'm here
to speak with Manager Zhen.
Why are there so many people?
Gentlemen, is something wrong?
Manager Zhen,
I'm not one to beat around the bush.
Today,
in front of all these people,
please give us a clear answer—
Is Li Ink going to switch
to planting tung trees
and producing oil soot ink?
Since you're all our own people,
I won't hide it from you.
Yes,
the Tian family holds an official order
and is forcibly taking the pine timber.
We have no choice but to hand it over.
And now that the pine wilt disease
is rampant outside,
pinewood is extremely hard to come by.
The only way to reduce our losses
is to switch to producing oil soot ink.
Manager Zhen,
this is not something
that can be changed easily.
Li Ink's foundation is pine soot ink.
Even if we can produce oil soot ink,
it won't give us any advantage.
The risk is too great.
Please reconsider, Manager Zhen.
I understand your concerns.
This decision to switch to oil soot ink
was made after careful consideration.
Everyone,
Li Ink is going through
a difficult time right now.
But as long as we stay united,
the business will gradually
get back on track.
I hope you can trust me.
So after all that,
it's just your own wishful thinking.
Let me ask you this—
did the Sixth Branch Master
agree to such a drastic change?
Right now, all of us
have doubts about your decision.
How can we stay united?
Today,
we're here for an explanation.
If you insist
on going your own way,
then we'll have no choice but to resign.
Don't you agree, everyone?
Yes, yes!
Mr. Liu!
What are you talking about?
Zhen.
Eldest Aunt, why are you here?
I came to bring you some pastries.
What is going on here?
Eldest Young Lady, please be the judge.
Can switching to producing oil soot ink
really save Li Ink?
Do you believe it?
We don't believe it!
We would rather work somewhere else.
Don't you agree?
Yes!
We'll work somewhere else!
Calm down, everyone!
Don't be so agitated.
Talk it over with Zhen.
There's always a solution.
Eldest Young Lady,
we are completely loyal to Li Ink.
Actually,
we just don't trust this new manager.
Pardon my bluntness.
The new manager
is too young.
How much has she experienced?
I beg you, Eldest Young Lady,
to make a decision.
Have Manager Zhen hand over power
to the Sixth Branch Master.
We cannot let her act arbitrarily anymore.
If the Sixth Branch Master
returns as manager,
we will have no complaints.
If she remains in charge,
we will have to quit.
That's right!
If Manager Zhen steps down, we'll stay!
Right?
Yes, step down!
Step down! Step down! Step down!
How dare you!
Everyone, calm down!
I understand.
You are all doing this
out of concern for Li Ink.
I know it well.
But switching to oil soot ink now
is the most practical solution.
Right now,
there really is no other way.
I
will not back down.
Nor will I step down.
To be honest,
I don't want you to leave.
However,
I can't dictate your thoughts.
Those who want to stay,
I welcome you.
In the future, Li Ink
will treat you well.
But if you want to leave
and find a better job,
I won't hold you back.
Let's part on good terms.
Steward Shao.
For those who want to leave,
please settle their accounts
and prepare red envelopes.
Don't make it difficult for them.
Alright, the matter is settled.
You can leave now.
What's wrong?
Is there something inappropriate?
If we really leave the Li family,
where else can we go?
Yeah. That's right.
There are so many ink workshops
in Huizhou.
You think we can't find a place to go?
Eldest Young Lady.
Steward Shao.
You've all seen it clearly.
We tried to persuade her nicely,
but she insists on having her way,
ignoring the foundation of the Li family.
I am powerless to help.
In that case,
we have no choice but to quit.
Farewell.
Move!
Mr. Liu!
Let's go!
-Mr. Liu!
Mr. Liu! Mr. Liu!
Mr. Liu.
Alright.
Dismissed. Stop looking.
Those who want to quit,
go to Steward Shao.
Those who don't want to quit,
stay and keep working.
Dismissed.
Zhen.
So many workers want to quit.
This is no small matter.
Why don't you
discuss it with your Uncle Jingdong?
What do you think?
Eldest Aunt, do you trust me?
If some people want to leave,
forcing them to stay
will make it hard for them
to work with us wholeheartedly.
Rest assured.
I will handle this matter properly.
When the time is right,
I will definitely give you an explanation.
Manager Zhen.
Eldest Young Lady.
Master Qi has returned.
He said he brought some people
selling tung tree seedlings
to see you.
Let's go.
Eldest Aunt, I'll go first.
Go ahead.
Uncle Jingdong.
What on earth is going on, Zhen?
Be careful.
[Resignation]
Don't worry. Let's sit down and talk.
Come. Be careful.
Today, the workers
came in crowds to quit.
I couldn't tell them
about the rosin oil plan.
Rather than
wasting my breath arguing with them,
I might as well play along
and put on this show of discord
to the fullest.
You mean
this is also a show for the Tian family?
Exactly.
It's a show for the Tian family.
We need the Tian family to truly believe
that Li Ink has reached a dead end,
and because I advocated
giving up the pine timber
and insisted on
planting tung trees instead,
I've become a target of the family.
This show
matches our previous plan.
The purpose
is to reduce the Tian family's doubts
even further.
As for that Liu,
ever since Li Ink
suffered losses this year,
he has been slacking off at work.
The laborers under him
have all been in cahoots with him.
I've long had it out for them.
Now that these people are gone,
I actually feel relieved.
Be that as it may,
there are still those
master craftsmen who are loyal to Li Ink.
They will inevitably
have doubts in their hearts.
How about I tell them the truth?
No.
Right now is the most crucial moment
in our battle with the Tian family.
We can't be soft-hearted just because
of a temporary difficulty.
The matter of mortgaging the farmland
back then
was spread by that Tian Jiangyue...
that Fourth Aunt.
That
caused us a lot of trouble.
Therefore,
we can't make the same mistake again.
It's not that I don't trust
those craftsmen,
but this plan leaves no room for error.
We must play it safe.
To be honest,
Mr. Ma and Mr. Qin
have already come to me.
I almost wore my lips out talking
just to calm them down.
Uncle Jingdong.
Why don't you continue
playing along with this show?
To outsiders,
we are already at odds with each other.
Why not take advantage
of today's disturbance
and add fuel to the fire?
You go and bring those master craftsmen
to your side,
and then make me a complete target
and make a few more scenes.
Firstly, it's for the Tian family to see.
Secondly,
it will make those craftsmen think
that you, Uncle Jingdong,
are backing them up.
Then they will naturally feel at ease.
It's a good idea,
but you will have to suffer
a grievance again.
Uncle Jingdong.
We just want what's the best for Li Ink.
This little grievance is nothing.
You're not angry anymore?
I'm not angry anymore.
How was it?
It worked.
Just as you expected.
With Mr. Liu taking the lead,
the master craftsmen at the ink workshop
couldn't sit still.
In the past few days,
Mr. Ma, Mr. Qin, and others
have gone to consult the Master every day.
They are planning to strike together
to force Li Zhen to give up power.
Heaven has truly not let me down.
Let them make some more trouble.
When Li Zhen can no longer hold on,
I will ask the clan elders to step in
and kick her out of the Li family
completely.
[Champion of Ink Making]
These are the samples
of the pine soot ink I designed
for Sage Qing He.
Father,
how do you like them?
Good,
very good.
Once we get the Li family's pine timber,
we can start working immediately.
But with the Li family's condition...
The Li family is definitely done for.
Father, don't worry.
Benchang,
I just asked around on the streets.
Li Ink has long been
at the end of its rope.
They started mortgaging
their lands and shops to raise money.
That's not all.
A few days ago,
one of their master craftsmen
quit his job.
And today,
half of the ink-makers went on strike.
They made a fuss along with Li Jingdong,
demanding that Li Zhen step down.
I'm afraid their entire family right now
in a state of panic and total chaos.
Benchang,
your move is quite good.
It fulfilled Sage Qing He's wish
and crushed Li Ink.
It really is
killing two birds with one stone.
Benchang,
you have to make a decision soon.
The Sage
has sent another letter urging us,
asking for his pine soot ink.
Right.
Right now, the whole Li family
is at a dead end.
Even if the Linxi pine yard
is given to them,
Li Zhen doesn't have the ability
to keep it.
After going around in a circle,
it will still come back to our family.
Right now, in the entire Li family,
only Li Zhen is willing to hand over
the pine timber.
If Li Jingdong and those master craftsmen
really drive Li Zhen out of the Li family,
it will be absolutely impossible
for us to get it.
Bensheng.
There's no time to lose.
Prepare the contract
and send it to the Li family immediately.
While they haven't recovered yet,
let's get the pine timber.
I'll go right now.
Here.
[Contract]
Ancestors bless us.
My father's efforts were not in vain.
Our Li Ink is saved.
The...
The lampblack made from rosin oil
is no worse than that made from
pine timber itself.
Manager Zhen,
your method is truly brilliant.
Whether it's the lampblack
or the ink made from it,
it's no worse than pine soot ink.
Eldest Aunt,
Steward Shao,
and gentlemen.
The matter of rosin oil
concerns the survival of Li Ink.
Uncle Jingdong and I
thought about it again and again
and didn't dare to tell everyone lightly.
I lied to you first.
I, Zhen,
apologize to you.
Please don't.
Zhen, please get up.
Everyone understands your intentions.
How could we blame you?
Manager Zhen, please sit.
Masters,
about hiding this matter,
I also knew about it.
You've been kept in the dark
these past few days,
so you must be feeling bad.
I also apologize to you,
all the craftsmen,
Sister-in-law, and Steward Shao,
for this.
Jingdong.
Master, you're being too serious.
You and Manager Zhen have thought things
through very carefully.
Well...
It was us who,
after listening to Liu's instigation,
had improper intentions.
If anyone should apologize,
it should be us.
That's because
you were worried about Li Ink
and have deep feelings for it.
All you craftsmen
are indispensable to Li Ink.
In this crisis,
you have stood by Li Ink through it all.
I will always remember it.
Come in.
Manager Zhen,
the Tian family sent someone to ask.
They want to know
when the pine timber will be delivered.
The pine timber Sixth Grandfather
sacrificed his life for—
the Tian family
won't get it so easily.
Brother!
Father!
Go and take a look!
See how the Li family
delivered the pine timber!
Let's go!
Father!
Stop it! Stop it!
Li Zhen, Li Jingdong!
What are you doing?
We're delivering the pine timber,
and also sending off Sixth Grandfather
who died for it!
Wait. What do you mean by this?
Aren't you doing this on purpose
just to disgust us?
How can our Tian family
do business in the future?
Unload the pine timber!
-Unload the pine timber!
Who dares!
No entry!
Step aside! Step aside!
What are you doing?
Who dares?
Bastards!
Sixth Grandfather, rest in peace!
-Rest in peace!
Sixth Master, rest in peace!
Sixth Grandfather, rest in peace!
Rest in peace!
You bastard!
Sixth Master, rest in peace!
Rest in peace!
The Sixth Master of the Li family
just died.
How could the Tian family do such a thing?
From now on,
it's better to deal with them less.
Rest in peace!
Sixth Grandfather!
Sixth Master, rest in peace!
Rest in peace!
-Rest in peace!
Sixth Master, rest in peace!
Li Jinhe, the head of the Sixth Branch,
was a man of exceptional virtue,
filial piety, and integrity.
His blessings were as vast as the sea,
and his achievements were remarkable.
Today, I, Li Jingdong,
a member of the Li family,
along with our clansmen,
am opening the ancestral hall
to inform our ancestors about this.
[Guangyu Hall]
We're hanging his portrait
in Li's Ancestral Hall.
[In Memory of Jinhe of the Li Family]
We hope our ancestors' virtues
will bless us forever.
Please accept these modest offerings.
Everyone lied to me.
They all lied to me.
Everyone in this family
treats me like an outsider.
They are all in league
with that girl from the Eighth Branch!
Who is it?
What do you want?
Fourth Young Lady.
Zhen wants to speak with you
in the main hall.
Fine.
I was just about to look for her too.
It's time to settle things with her.
What is it?
Do you have nothing to say to everyone?
Sister-in-law,
you were the ones who called me here.
And now you're asking me?
Leaking the news of mortgaging
the fields to the ink merchants
and inciting Mr. Liu
to resign to shake morale
were all your doing, right?
Yes.
So what?
Let me make it clear today.
Li Zhen,
I don't trust you at all,
nor do I accept you
taking charge of Li Ink.
Tian Jiangyue.
You speak without thinking
and have repeatedly
harmed Li Ink's interests.
Today, as the head of the family,
I fine you a year's allowance
and ground you for a month.
How dare you!
It's not about whether I dare,
but that in this family now,
I have the final say.
Third Brother, Sister-in-law,
are you just going to let her
treat me like this?
When Mother was in charge,
she never even scolded me once.
Tian Jiangyue,
you've gone too far this time.
Considering you lost your husband,
we've let you have your way for years.
But this time,
in the family's moment of crisis,
you kicked us when we were down.
You know that I hate traitors
more than anything in my life.
So this time,
I can't help you.
Fine.
I see.
Now I understand everything.
In this family, I'm just an outsider.
Getting rid of me
will satisfy you, won't it?
Every single one of you is full of lies.
You've deceived me for so many years,
just waiting for the Eighth Branch
to return to the clan,
so you could kick me out.
Then you'd still be one big happy family.
Enough!
Tian Jiangyue!
Your punishment
is based entirely on your actions.
You are the one who did wrong.
My only mistake is living until now,
being an eyesore to all of you!
You are teaming up to humiliate me.
I might as well die right now...
to give you what you want!
Tian Jiangyue, what are you doing?
Jiangyue!
Don't touch me!
Let go!
Third Aunt, don't stop her!
Let her die.
Go ahead.
Didn't you want to die?
Do it!
What?
Are you scared?
Are you a coward?
Li Zhen,
I'll take you down with me!
Li Zhen!
Take her away!
Let me go!
Li Zhen!
You are the daughter of a murderer!
You have a murderer's blood in your veins.
Take her away!
How many lives will you take
from the Li family
before you stop?
Let me go!
Li Jingdong, you are a man!
But you've been
following a girl around every day
to make a living!
What dignity do you have left?
And Sister-in-law!
Don't think I don't know!
You were also kept in the dark
about the pine timber exchange!
This girl lied to you today.
She will lie to you about everything
from now on!
Let go of me!